<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://docbook.org/xml/5.0CR3/rng/docbookxi.rng"
schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<!--
<?xml-model href="http://docbook.org/xml/5.1CR3/rng/docbook.rng"
            schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
-->
<!DOCTYPE book [
<!ENTITY % myent SYSTEM "Entities.ent">
<!ENTITY % pc SYSTEM "pc.ent">
%myent;
%pc;
]>
<book xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
  xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" xml:id="book.publican_creators" xml:lang="en" version="5.0">
  <info>
    <title>How to use publican_creators</title>
    <productnumber>&VERSION;</productnumber>
    <productname>publican_creators</productname>
    <subtitle>A graphical user interface for publican and fo2xxx</subtitle>
    <releaseinfo>Version 1.2.2 - Revision: 0</releaseinfo>
    <date>
      <?dbtimestamp format="B d, Y"?>
    </date>
    <authorgroup>
      <author>
        <personname><firstname>Sascha</firstname>
          <surname>Manns</surname>
        </personname>
        <affiliation>
          <orgname/>
          <orgdiv/>
        </affiliation>
        <email>Sascha.Manns@mailbox.org</email>
      </author>
    </authorgroup>
    <legalnotice>
      <para>Copyright <trademark class="copyright"/> 2018 Sascha Manns </para>
      <para>Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this document under the terms of
        the GNU Free Documentation License, Version 1.3 or any later version published by the Free
        Software Foundation; with no Invariant Sections, no Front-Cover Texts, and no Back-Cover
        Texts. A copy of the license is included in the section entitled "GNU Free Documentation
        License". The latest version is also presently available at <link
          xlink:href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/fdl.txt"
          >http://www.gnu.org/licenses/fdl.txt</link>. </para>
      <para>All programs, presentation and information contained in this document have been to best
        of our knowledge. However, errors cannot be completely ruled out. For this reason, the
        material contained in this document implies no obligation or warranty connected ANY KIND.
        The authors and publishers assume no responsibility as a result and any resulting liability
        will assume that the in some way from Using this material, or parts thereof, or
        infringements of third parties arise. </para>
      <para>The use of general descriptive names, trade names, trademarks, etc. in this book even if
        not explicitly, does not justify the assumption that such names are Sense of the trademark
        and trade protection laws would have to be regarded as free and therefore may be used by
        anyone. All trade names are no guaranteed freedom Used use and are possibly registered trademarks. The author and Publisher are aimed essentially follows the notations of the
        manufacturers. others here products mentioned may be trademarks of their respective owners. </para>
      <para>This document has been set in the Arezzo Pro Light and Stafford Pro Light Font family by
        daps (<link xlink:href="https://github.com/openSUSE/daps"
          xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">https://github.com/openSUSE/daps</link>).
      </para>
    </legalnotice>
    <abstract>
      <para>
        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject role="fo">
            <imagedata fileref="hicolor_apps_64x64_publican_creators.png" width="100%"
              align="center"/>
          </imageobject>
          <imageobject role="html">
            <imagedata fileref="hicolor_apps_64x64_publican_creators.png" width="100%"
              align="center"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject> This program works on top of Redhat's <application>publican</application>. It
        helps you create new projects and replaces the default content with your own information.
        This is done by <productname>publican_creators</productname> using a graphical project
        developer, a build script and a graphical revision editor. In addition to the output formats
        supported by <application>publican</application>,
          <productname>publican_creators</productname> supports the formats docx, odt, rtf and wml
        (using the XFC FO- converter). </para>
    </abstract>
  </info>
  <chapter xml:id="cha.about">
    <info>
      <title>Round about</title>
    </info>
    <para>
      <productname>publican_creators</productname> is a graphical tool for creating new DocBook projects. It is
      mainly directed at DocBook users, who are confronted daily with new DocBook projects.
      <application>Publican</application> has proven to be a popular tool to create and manage
      projects. For example, large Linux distributions such as Redhat, Fedora and Debian are
      already using <application>publican</application> for their documentation.
    </para>
    <para>I created <productname>publican_creators</productname> as a tool from DocBook authors for DocBook
      authors. <productname>publican_creators</productname> now offers the possibility to start new projects,
      add new revisions and build the project.
    </para>
    <xi:include href="common_intro_typografie.xml"/>
    <xi:include href="common_intro_feedback.xml"/>
    <xi:include href="common_intro_making.xml"/>
    <xi:include href="common_intro_source_code.xml"/>
  </chapter>
  <xi:include href="Introduction.xml" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>
  <xi:include href="Configuration.xml" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>
  <xi:include href="Using.xml" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>
  <xi:include href="Revision.xml" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>
  <xi:include href="TheBuildscript.xml" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
  <xi:include href="app.revision_update.xml"/>
  <xi:include href="app.gfdl.xml"/>
  <index/>
</book>
